On travel insurance, you will apply for Samsung Visa Mostly or Visa, otherwise travel insurance is
retirement, in some countries it is not retirement, but still you
must consider travel insurance, there is a big logical reason behind it, many people think Yes, I have existing
medical insurance, it will be reduced even outside, but it will not be reduced outside
, it becomes invalid as soon as you leave India.
If you take a travel insurance of 700-800, then
it will cover you to a great extent, otherwise if your passport is in any other country, then
you can spend a lot of money. Third most important Thing is if you go to any country by chase
late exam i go to malaysia malaysia's health infra
is very expensive for those who are non resident so by default mistake even if i got insured na i lost lot of
money So you should definitely consider travel insurance of a good company, whether it is mandatory or not, I
purchase from where to buy, where not to buy is your personal choice, I will
tell you three to four places from where you will find the best suit If you can purchase from there, then you search on Google for
simple travel insurance, so many quotations will be available to you, you can purchase from any company
whose saree company is good, I have also taken IG's I have also taken the digital one,
I have also taken the rest of the lampbot and Reliance General Insurance, ok, now you have to
compare all these, then you go to the policy market, which is fine, in the policy market, which country are you traveling? Ho
late I am going to travel to malaysia select again late hoon decide your date off let's decide
from 17th whatever your date is ok its 29 days trip if you
want to take family whole family If yes, then you can also take sour here so that the person who is insured or with whom that
urgency is created, he can redeem it
. If there is no medical condition, there is nothing in the recesh, then
here he is asking for the pay number, now all these are shown from here, now based on your need, according to how much tax you
need or what you want inside the tax, according to that you You can tighten it, if you want to
add any type of coverage, etc., then you can simply add it from here, if you want to
define the purpose, then it is able to give me this, on the basis of example, here Pay OTP will come on my number,
I confirmed, after that I verified my address etc. my passport because I already
had the details, then passport was also received and after confirming payment option will come and it will be confirmed.